We are the victims here.
We are being victimized by a very greedy entity.
I am shocked by the way the people that we have been in business with are treating us.
I cannot believe it, quite frankly, how far apart we are on so many things.
How they plead poverty, that they are losing money left and right when giving hundreds
of millions of dollars to their CEOs.
The entire business model has been changed by streaming, digital, AI.
This is a moment of history that is a moment of truth.
If we don't stand tall right now, we are all going to be in trouble.
We are all going to be in jeopardy of being replaced by machines.
You cannot change the business model as much as it has changed and not expect the contract
to change too.
We are not going to keep doing incremental changes on a contract that no longer honors what is
happening right now with this business model that was foisted upon us.
What are we doing, moving around furniture on the Titanic?
It's crazy.